Opportunity rocks.
The Rocker is a comedy, music film directed by Peter Cattaneo.
In the 1980s, a drummer is abandoned by his band just
before they become rock superstars.
Twenty years later, the drummer sees his second chance at stardom arise when he is
asked to perform with his teenage nephew's high school rock band.
Robert 'Fish' Fishman, played by Rainn Wilson.
Curtis, played by Teddy Geiger.
Matt Gadman, played by Josh Gad.
Amelia, played by Emma Stone.
Kim, played by Christina Applegate.
Stan, played by Jeff Garlin.
The Rocker is a 2008 American comedy film directed by Peter Cattaneo and written
by Maya Forbes and Wallace Wolodarsky, from a story by Ryan Jaffe.
The film stars Rainn Wilson as a failed musician who goes on tour with
his nephew's band after one of their songs goes viral.
Christina Applegate, Jeff Garlin, Josh Gad, Teddy
Geiger and Emma Stone also star.
The Rocker was released on August 20, 2008, and
received mixed reviews from critics.
It grossed $7 million against a $15 million budget.
The film explores themes of rock 'n' roll, 1970s, drums, groupie, heavy metal.
The tone is lighthearted.